Yakanta Idol
Now we have this main YouTube section.
Please give a cute title call.
My three main elements!
Yay!
Thank you very much.
This corner is to introduce the three elements that make Serritara-san what she is.
Through this corner, I would like to get to know Ms. Serritara better.
Now, please present your three elements.
Ta-da!
Food
2. family
3. carelessness.
I see!
Food!
Yes, I like to eat quite a bit. I like to eat a lot.
That's why I often eat before a live concert,
Also, this picture is miso soup.
You! You!
You should definitely make unique pictures of girls into goods.
Even if it has one point, it's cute.
Really?
The reason why I chose miso soup is because I really like miso soup,
I used to drink it a lot before live performances and before filming,
But recently I noticed that it causes swelling before a photo shoot,
But recently I noticed that it causes swelling before a shoot, so I stopped drinking it before a shoot,
Did you notice it recently?
Yes, I did. I had been thinking about it for a while,
But it took me quite a bit of time to drink,
But I didn't want to shoot with a swollen face,
So I stopped drinking. I cut back on it.
There are many kinds of miso soup.
What is your favorite ingredient?
I like nameko mushrooms, which are sold at convenience stores.
Nameko mushrooms?
In a cup.
When I'm making up, I can drink it in the best way.
I see. If it's a vegetable dish, do you need chopsticks?
That's right.
I don't eat many vegetables.
I'm sorry. Are you the type of person who doesn't eat vegetables?
I do, but I don't eat vegetables in miso soup.
Vegetables in miso soup?
I don't have much of a chance to eat them,
I don't have a chance to eat them.
That's why I like nameko mushrooms.
Funghi?
I like nameko mushrooms.
Of course, I love miso soup at home,
I like the one at home, too,
But what I really liked the most was..,
There was a miso soup vending machine at the office until recently, right?
There it is!
That was my favorite. What was that vending machine?
What was that vending machine?
They were buying kuramucha for me,
Wait a minute. That was the manager himself,
Some of the talent was wearing them over there.
Really?
You should put it on a sticky note and request for it.
You should do it.
I was the one who changed it,
I had a cup of Kuramu tea,
I was a little shocked,
I'm going to join the movement.
Really?
Miso soup is gone,
I heard that you should have noticed it earlier,
There is a vending machine at my office,
There is a button for miso soup in the vending machine at our office.
It was there.
I liked it,
I told my fans about it.
I told my fans that I liked the vending machine at the office better,
But it was different,
I have my wish.
It was delicious, wasn't it?
It was really good.
You could drink from it.
It was amazing.
I was a little shocked.I was a little shocked.
That was the best?
That was really the best.
I'm sorry about that, Mom.
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no.
Mom's going to eat a little bit of it?
I was like, "Are you serious?
Yes, that's right.
I'm nervous. Like the other members.
Like, "There you are.
Thank you! Bye-bye Ron!